

Emmanuel Olatunbosun

Certified Full-Stack Web Developer | UI/UX Designer | SEO Expert

Personal Info

- emmanuelolatunbosun020@g mail.com
- C +1 523 748 0457
- Vernon, Connecticut, United States

EDUCATION

- Master of Computer
 Science (MSCS), Computer
 engineering
 Harvard University
 Aug 2017 Jun 2019
- Bachelor of Computer
 Science (B.CompSc),
 Computer science
 Stanford University
 Feb 2012 Oct 2016

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- ← CSS Expert
- ✓ SEO Audit Expert
- JavaScript, React framework, jQuery - Expert

Summary

I am a full stack web developer with over 5 years of expertise designing and developing WordPress, Wix, and Shopify websites. If you want to use digital transformation to accelerate growth and unleash the potential of your business to be more productive and lucrative, I am ready to help.

I provide a wide range of services, including web development, design, graphic design, SEO, and digital marketing. A COMPLETE SOLUTION IS JUST ONE CLICK AWAY!

Why should you employ me?

- ∠ Quick turnaround
- ✓ Digital Marketer with Certification and Experience
- Work accurately, carefully, and on time
- Customer Satisfaction Guaranteed
- ∠ Rapid Reaction

PREVIOUS WORK EXPERIENCE

Full-stack web Developer, State Street Global Advisors, United States November 2020 - January 2023

- Scripted and coded for various projects including Perl, Visual Basic, and Java.
- Organizing and participating in weekly conference calls with project stakeholders and IT professionals

Senior Software Engineer , Lexington Solutions, LLC, United States April 2019 - March 2020

- Contributed to the development the "Fusion" program by developing code on both the client and server sides.
- Participated in a number of code reviews with co-developers.

SEO Specialist, Serial Scaling (Freelance)

April 2021 - October 2022

 Research intriguing keywords for each webpage to rank the website using SurferSEO or Semrush. Those keywords will be less competitive than others..